Opportunity rocks where you least expect it.
Rock the Kasbah is a comedy, music, war film directed by Barry Levinson.
A washed-up music producer finds one last shot at redemption
with a golden-voiced young girl in Afghanistan.
However, when jealousy gets the better of a disgruntled ex-boyfriend, he
decides to oppose the young star with talent of his own.
Richie Lanz, played by Bill Murray.
Ronnie, played by Zooey Deschanel.
Bombay Brian, played by Bruce Willis.
Merci, played by Kate Hudson.
Private Barnes, played by Taylor Kinney.
Nick, played by Danny McBride.
Rock the Kasbah is a 2015 American comedy film directed by
Barry Levinson and written by Mitch Glazer.
The film stars Bill Murray as a talent manager sent to Afghanistan for a USO tour, Kate Hudson as his partner in
country, Bruce Willis as his armed protection and book client, and Leem Lubany as his musical discovery.
Open Road Films released the film on October 23, 2015.
The film explores themes of jealousy, ex-boyfriend,
redemption, afghanistan, record producer.
The tone is lighthearted.